webix.com 2019-03-07

# JavaScript Library Webix - Privacy Policy

##### Last updated May 24, 2018

Webix acknowledges the importance of keeping your personal data safe and private. In order to ensure your privacy safety we’ve developed this Privacy Policy covering the collection, usage and retention of your personal information that we may perform. This Privacy Policy is aimed at your safe stay on https://webix.com website (“Site”) as well as your private data safety while using our products or services. If you find our Privacy Policy statements inappropriate for you, we recommend you to refrain from using our website, software products or services.

### What Information is Collected

You may visit our Site without identifying yourself or revealing any personal data. However, during your stay on our Site your non-personal data (browser type, IP address, operating system, website access times and referring website addresses on its servers., etc.) may be collected via third party analytics tools, which are described in the next chapters. This data is anonymous and website users can’t be identified through it.

If you subscribe to Webix blog, you should provide only your email address.

When you download Webix trial version you are asked to enter your full name and email address.

When you create an account at Webix forum you are asked to enter your email address.

When buying Webix library you are asked to enter your private data onto a secured page. This data includes your full name, email address, postal address, phone number and credit card information.

### Why Information is Collected

Your personal data that we collect helps us provide you with the most relevant website content and user experience as well as high quality products or services. We may use your personal data for the two main purposes:

  1. We use information that you provide when you download Webix trial version for keeping you informed about Webix product.

  2. The email address provided by you during the acquisition of Webix product may be used by us for sending out information and updates related to your order as well as service information.

Apart from that, we may use your private data in order to:

  * Keep you updated about: Webix product, new releases, features, technical support, license information, any changes to Webix terms and conditions etc.
  * Get your feedback on using Webix product or services
  * Offer you to participate in a promotion or contest to get Webix product or services or conduct other marketing communications
  * Perform any other communication with you needed to provide you with the necessary information concerning Webix that you’re interested in

### Information Needed For Processing Orders

When buying Webix product you’re redirected to the website of our third party e-commerce provider PayProGlobal (Provider). As claimed by our Provider, it has been certified as an accredited Level 1 Service Provider after having passed a comprehensive auditing process conducted by GRSee Consulting, an independent Quality Security Assessor (QSA). PCI-DSS is the worldwide information security standard established by the Payment Card Industry Security Standards Council, which guarantees full security of sensitive data and protection against risks of fraud.

In order to make a purchase you need to provide such personal data as your name, email address, postal address, phone number and company name. If you choose to pay by credit or debit card, you’ll be also asked to enter its credentials. This information is necessary for our third party e-commerce platform to process your order and complete your payment. Once your payment is processed, you will receive confirmatory documents (receipts, invoices, payment confirmation) from our provider. Our provider will send us only the information needed for fulfilling your order on our part: name, email address, company name, telephone number and Order ID assigned to your purchase (this Order ID is your License ID). This information will let us send you the relevant license information, the download link to the software product and your credentials to login to the Clients Area and Support Center. We do not receive and/or collect your payment data (the credentials of your credit card or some other payment information).

### How to Manage Your Private Data

If you don’t want to receive email notifications from Webix, you can unsubscribe from the Webix newsletter. The unsubscribe instructions are placed at the bottom of each email you receive.

You also have the right to request the deletion of your private data that you have provided to us downloading Webix trial version or purchasing Webix product. To do so, please, send us a request at . We will remove your data within 30 days after the request was submitted.

### Google Analytics

We use Google Analytics (<https://www.google.com/analytics/>), a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc, to analyze our website visitors’ behavior for the sole purpose of improving the quality of Webix products and services. Google Analytics makes use of cookies to analyze our website traffic data and your activities on our Site. By using this Site, you consent to information being collected by Google in said manner for the aforementioned purposes. However, you can opt-out of being tracked by Google Analytics anytime: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.

### Yandex Metrika

Yandex Metrica helps us to gather statistical data about visitors' behaviour on our Site such as mouse clicks, mouse movements, scrolling activity, etc. By analysing the received statistics, we’re aimed at improving the user experience of our Site. To learn more about Yandex Metrica, visit <https://metrica.yandex.com/about>. To opt out of Yandex Metrika tracking system visit: [Yandex.Metrica opt-out add-on](https://yandex.com/support/metrica/general/opt-out.html).

Based on data collected by Google Analytics we may also build custom audiences of people who have visited some of our Site’s pages and/or made a conversion on our Site for showing these audiences relevant ads with the help of Google Adwords Remarketing feature. This process doesn’t involve using any of your personal data. Your personal data is not being disclosed or transferred in any way to Google. You may adjust your preferences connected to Google Adwords ads you want or don’t want to see here: <https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/authenticated>.

### Cookies

Session cookies (small text fragments stored on a visitor's computer or device) are used on our Site to memorize if a user is a returning one and what his/her login details for an online cabinet are if he/she gave permission to our Site for remembering them. Cookies are usually enabled by default, but you can check your browser settings and disable them yourself. It’s also possible to delete all cookies stored on your computer or device at any moment. However, disabling cookies may affect your user experience on our website.

### Information security

We take all appropriate measures to ensure the security of your personal data when you purchase Webix product or subscribe to our newsletter. All private information entered by you is transferred via special security systems and automatically encrypted using SSL (Sockets Layer Protocol). SSL is the industry standard for transferring sensitive data over the internet. Access to your personal information is restricted to those Webix employees who need to have access to it and bear responsibility for keeping your information confidential.

### Sharing Your Personal Data

We do not sell, rent or give out personal information to any third party. We may involve third party service providers to assist us in conducting our business (for instance, sending marketing newsletters or surveys) and share with them some of your private data necessary for that purpose if you have given us your consent and if the third party agrees to keep this information confidential. We will not use your information for any purpose outside the scope of communicating with you about our products and services.

### Links to Third Party Websites

You may find links to third party websites (our partners, resellers, etc.) on our Site. We don’t take any responsibility for the content of these websites or for your security on them. Ensuring your privacy rights on third party websites is governed by third party Privacy Policies.

### Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your private data if we’re obliged to do so by legal authorities (in connection with demands from governmental authorities or legal and contractual disputes) or protecting our rights because of the violation of our terms of use, fraud or other security issues.

### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

Should our online Privacy Policy change at any time, we will place the changes on this page and notify you of important changes via email. The date when the latest changes happen can be found at the top of this page. We also recommend you to check our Privacy Policy page yourself from time to time.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions concerning this Privacy Policy or your private data security, please write us at .
